In this tutorial video, we use the 11th version of Doshi Marvelous Designer.
If you need to learn the 10th version of Marvelous Designer, please watch the previous video.
In order to make it easier to learn, we will use Doshi's default standard mouse preset.
In this tutorial, we will learn how to use a variety of powder line tools.
First, we need to delete all the powder lines created in the 3D window.
If you have a project file that does not contain powder lines, you can also use it.
Select the Edit Powder Line Tool in the 2D window.
Press the left mouse button and drag the mouse to select all the powder lines in the frame, then press the Delete button to delete them.
Please note that after selecting the Edit Powder Line Tool, you can press Ctrl A to select all the powder lines.
This selection of all the frame keys is almost applicable to all the editing tools of Marvelous Designer.
In the 3D window, switch to the Move Tool.
Select all the 3D window panels and click to reset the 3D arrangement position.
Then the panel will return to the position when it was just set up before the simulation.
First, select the Line Powder Tool, and then create the two sets of powder lines in the front and back.
Then switch to the Free Powder Tool under the Powder Tool drop-down menu.
The Free Powder Tool is not limited by the separation point of the line section.
You can choose the starting and ending positions of the powder lines at will.
Back to Tissue, we first click on the top point of the side powder line in the front, then move the mouse along the direction of the powder line, then click on the bottom point.
Now we need to select the line section on the other side of the powder line.
As you select the Edit Powder Line Tool in the second section, you will see a blue dot when you move the mouse.
This means that it is in the same position as the other side of the powder line from the Edit Powder Line Tool.
But as I said before, when you are using the Free Powder Tool, you can choose the Edit Powder Line Tool at will.
If you want to use the method multi-layer blue dot at will.
You can choose items by narration export the selected item from thescale file at will and work it'shorn.
Hope you will enjoy it!
Please make sure that you are using a供应素 variator when you create a corne blockchain.
This will help you to smoothly create the condition and understand.
Tracing the three-dimensional function window, you'll see that the corne dot shows up while you place the switch to merge.
Please take a look at the function, as I will show it again.
Click the relation icon at the bottom right corner of the screen.
Please type Черge.
Continue to use the free sewing tool to sew the side seams of the shoulder line and the sleeve, and get used to the operation steps.
Next is the sewing of the sleeve and the sleeve, we will use the nbn free sewing tool.
The sewing line tool will help us to sew the multiple root lines and the multiple root lines.
Therefore, it is not necessary to create multiple sewing lines.
When using this tool, we can immediately complete the sewing line between the sleeve and the sleeve.
To answer the question, first switch to the nbn sewing line.
This tool is almost the same as the free sewing tool.
You can freely select the starting point and the end point.
When choosing this tool, a prompt will pop up.
Click on it or click on it to start the free sewing of m.
First, like free sewing, select the sewing line.
At this time, you will see that the prompt becomes press the return to complete the sewing.
You can continue to choose the curve once.
For other lines, they will be formed in order.
M group sewing line, press the enter key to complete the selection.
So continue to select the line on the back and press the enter key after completion.
Please be sure to clarify the connection position of the sewing line and the direction of the seam.
The sewing line in the front and back is connected to each other by the shoulder and the outer point.
Therefore, the end and start positions are shoulder points.
Then we need to select the n group sewing line.
Since we started selecting from the bottom point in M group, the sleeve is also the same position.
You do not need to pause the selection in the middle.
Because the free sewing line is not limited to the straight line on the line section.
The same as the free sewing tool, there will also be an equal blue point.
Here we just need to click on the end point of the sleeve on the other side.
Then press the enter key to complete the m to n sewing line.
After completion, check the 3D window to see if there is an intersecting sewing line.
After the inspection, let's learn how to use the m to n sewing tool.
The application of this tool is similar to the sewing line.
When selecting this tool, a prompt will pop up.
Click on the line section to set the m sewing line.
After selecting a line, the prompt will change to press the return key to complete the m sewing line.
Similar to the m to n free sewing line, you can use it to make many line sections.
Let's try to use the free sewing line.
The free sewing line has two lines.
Let's try to finish the pocket sewing
Pay attention to the direction of the sewing line
After selecting the pocket panel line
Press the Enter key to confirm the selection
Next we have to select the line with their seam
Follow the order and seam direction
Click the inner line once
Then press the Enter key to complete the selection
Check the 3D window to ensure that there is no error between the sewing lines
After confirming that all the sewing lines are completed
Press the control button to start the simulation
Clothes will have the effect of gravity and sewing lines
Clothed on the virtual model
The more complicated the clothing, the longer the simulation time
The slower the simulation speed
If you need to stop the simulation
You can press the control button again or click the simulation button
Save the project file
We will use it in the following tutorial